[music]
[music] It
was hard to part with their comrades,
but for them the death of the colonel
marked the end of their journey and the beginning of a new
life on the shores of Lake Baikal.  For me,
this path became a boundary, a
boundary between the order and life, between
duty and the dream of seeing my father.
And just like Artyum, I chose my dream and
went after it.
On the way, it sometimes seemed to me that the
trees, runes, and leaning poles that remained behind me were
simply an endless
movie on a tattered screen.
And I am a midnight spectator, sitting in an empty
hall.
But each morning, rising directly in line with the
sun, brought a change of scenery,
instilling confidence that I was nevertheless
approaching the ocean.
One step, then another step and another,
despite any obstacles.
Someday, relaxing on the porch of my
father's house,
I might want to write a book about
this coming
someday, but not today.
I'm at the city where the
final stage of my journey is to begin,
and I can already smell the pestilence.  If I
really have a chance to get home, I will
find it here.
Hello, Vlade Vok
[music]
Better get lost.   Be
careful not to knock it over.
Shoot only at the legs, [ __ ].
I warn you, the
next shot will be to kill.
Hey, you, captain, [ __ ] come out with your
hands up.
What else do you need?
That's it, nothing more is needed.  You won't
fail, son.  The lawyer wants to take you alive
.
How do you know what he wants there?
There is such a thing, I understand.  In short, Sha,
Bazar, come out already.
Where should I go out?  Show yourself.
Come here,
thank you.
I think they're gone.
Thanks for your help.  Come up here.   Let's
chat.
Now.
Ah, [ __ ], I got you.
Where did you come from?
Come on, go
fly.
Anu, put the weapon away.
Woah, easy there.  I helped.
And I say, clean it up quickly.
Please, I don't need any trouble.  Yashch
ship, I need to go home.  You don't know anything
suitable here.
Well, we only have one ship, but it’s
suitable.  Come on, I'll show you.   Be
careful here, otherwise you'll end up with a
handsome guy.
Everyone is after me.  They want to serve before the commission
.
Well, at least we're holding back.
Well, go ahead and get it.  Do you see it over there?
Vaurine.
And how healthy she is.  A good ticket home.
By the way, where is your house?  Somehow your
accent seems suspiciously familiar to me.
Sandiego.
Oops, another American.  What do you have here
smeared with honey?
Another.
You really don't seem to know, so
I'll tell you, but later.
We're packing up.
What the hell?   I
noticed the wings.
Let's leave before we get hit.
Damn, we're late.
Get out of here.
A
[music]
Ah.
And
Policho already put your
hands up.
Come with us.
Rajivyeom.
Go to
kill
[music]
Yeah.   Back
off.
Oh,
leave me alone for now.
Well, have you jumped enough, bull?
And [ __ ].
Ah, [ __ ].   I'm
telling you exactly.  I heard him swearing
while they were tying him up.  [ __ ] and olol goats.  Hey, I'm
American.  This
Russian isn't very good.  How do you know it's
American?
Well, I don’t know, but I heard about it in the movies before the war
.
So he can too.
By the way, he came to his senses.
Hey, where are you from?
From Moscow.
Listen, you're not an American by any chance, are you?
No, damn, Buryats.
American.
Yeah, well you see,
someone tried to screw us over, but it didn't
help.
The day, I say, is not my day.
Looks like it.
Well, never mind, maybe you'll even be happy.
Guys, it turns out we
got an American.  I need to call the cat and report.
Wow.  Come on,
I'm a courier.  Give me the cat.  Here's news for
him.
He is not on the bridge, please wait.
Okay, let's wait.
Turn off the engine, bros.  We're waiting for the boss.
Frets.
By the way, regarding the question about not being your day.
See what's there?
I see.  Clouds.
Clouds.  This is brother Purya.
Exactly, Storm.  And they are not simple here.   If
you get into one of these, you'll be in trouble.
So we're lucky we accepted you.
Courier, boss on the bridge.  I'm switching to
it.
Good.
Get started and let's get on the boat.
Well, what's up, Urus?  Have you conveyed the proposal to the captain
?
No, some riff-raff scared him off, but there
was one guy with him.  We took it just in
case.  Turned out to be an American.
In your death?
You're insulting me, boss.  He swore like you do on your worst
days.
Give this American a rod.
America is
going crazy.
I don't really believe it myself.
Wow.  So that's it.  Couriers of
this guest.  Clear.  Bring him here quickly.
End of communication.
Eat.  Boss.   Do
you see the effect?  And who understood everything right away
?  Who said you're American?  Ah,
wow, our
healthy fool wax.   Yeah, right.
Look, it's the boss.
This is him.
It's me.
Why haven't they untied you?
And
now
I ask for a set.
Well, take the guest to the gangway.
There is a boss.
Damn, the cat is angry.   I
should have untied him right away.
Got it for untying.
Sometimes you can't please a cat at all.
Looks like this isn't our day.
Well, your patronymic has arrived.  Come
on board.
Otherwise it's time to hide.  The storm is about
to start.
So where do you want your ticket?
To Sanego
California.
This is where Paradise on earth was.  But if you don't
count the rush hour traffic, of course.
Listen, remind me, what was the
name of your baseball team?
Padres.
Exactly.  Our team played with them often.  I'm
with Atlas too.
Riners, that's if you still think I'm a prostitute
.
Nothing personal, Corporal.  Times are
so difficult right now.